SYAFIKIHIDAYAH

Web Developer

fikimantap@gmail.com | +62 85766224633 | http://bit.ly/porfoliofiki | https://linkedin.com/in/syafiki-hidayah | Batam, Kepulauan Riau

SUMMARY

I have an interest in the world of computer technology, one of which is programming. I like to learn new things about it, so I'm dedicated to be a reliable programmer. BNSP Certified as a Junior Web Developer. Even though I am a fresh graduate, I have the ability and experience in developing applications through 2 years as web developer with proficiency PHP language.

EXPERIENCE

Universitas Ibnu Sina - Batam

Lecturer Assistant (2021 - Now)

- During my time at university, I helped with the preparation of teaching materials and assisted with lectures and courses.
- Making software for thesis students or schools around Batam, about 20 applications were accomplished.

Kecamatan Batam Kota – Batam(Voluntary Work)

IT Support (October 2022–January 2023)

- Maintaining office computers, repair computer from a virus, set up printers and other peripherals.
- Make a letter management system application in the community empowerment section, an application may include whatsapp bussiness api.

PT. Selaras Mutiarasi – Bandung(Remote)

Fullstack Web Developer (June 2022 - May 2023)

- Building on previous developer work, projects that focus on advertising/networking websites are increasing the number of advertising domains so that they have a wide reach to visitors.
- Manage projects with teams using a variety of tools, including gitlab for version control and cloud hosting for website storage.
- Integrate any API's the one is STRIPE payment gateway, NLP Translation for translate whole page based on visitor country language
- Communicate as well with developer team and project owner.

EDUCATION

Universitas Ibnu Sina (2019 - 2023)

Bachelor Degree, Information Technology – GPA 3.84/4.00 (144 Credits)

Follow an organization called HMTI(*Himpunan Mahasiswa Teknik Informatika*), winning *Aruba Olympics* event we got TOP 10 grade, at the end my college I have got Best Graduate in Engineering Faculty Achievement

SKILLS

Hard Skills

HTML, CSS, PHP, JQuery, Bootstrap, Laravel, MySQL, Git, Javascript, REST API, Basic MEVN Stack(MongoDB, Express, Vue, NodeJS), SSH, FTP

Soft Skills

Communication, Time Management, Problem Solving

Language Skills

Bahasa Indonesia, Bahasa Inggris(Passive)

CERTIFICATE

- Junior Web Programmer BNSP
- Pemrograman PHP: Pemula Sampai Mahir Udemy
- TOEFL
- Best Graduation